<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- Data referenced from http://rdanderson.com/stargate/glyphs/glyphs.htm -->
<addresses>

    <address>
        <name>Abydos</name>
        <description>
            Abydos is a sandy desert planet with 36-hour days and two moons. Once ruled by Ra, the planet was home to
            the Abydonians who lived in simple villages and worked in the naquadah mines in the shadow of Ra's pyramid
            where the stargate is housed. Abydos is relatively close to Earth in the stargate network, making it
            possible to dial there without compensating for stellar drift. Thus it was the destination of the first
            stargate mission from Earth. With the discovery of a map room and an elaborate cartouche containing all the
            stargate addresses known to the Goa'uld, the necessary drift calculations could be made to successfully dial
            other planets.
        </description>
        <id_code></id_code>
        <symbols>27-7-15-32-12-30</symbols>
        <locked>false</locked>
    </address>

    <address>
        <name>Apophis' Base</name>
        <description>
            In the Book of the Dead from Egyptian mythology, Apophis was the serpent god who ruled the night, rival to
            his brother Ra, the sun god who ruled the day. The Goa'uld Apophis had taken as his host a scribe in the
            Temple of Amon at Karnak. Protected by an army of Serpent Guards, he rose to power as one of the Goa'uld
            System Lords. Among the worlds in his domain were Pangar, which he ruled for a time after defeating the
            System Lord Shak'ran, Cartago, where he harvested humans as hosts, Abydos, which he claimed after the death
            of Ra, and the Jaffa homeworld of Chulak. His loyal Jaffa wore the symbol of the serpent. For many years,
            Bra'tac had served as his First Prime, until Teal'c rose to the position and succeeded his mentor.
        </description>
        <id_code></id_code>
        <symbols>20-18-11-38-10-32</symbols>
        <locked>false</locked>
    </address>

    <address>
        <name>Camelot</name>
        <description>
            Camelot, a village on PX1-767, is considered to be the past and future home of King Arthur and his Round
            Table. The walled town is reminiscent of medieval England, and the public square prominently displays a
            sword embedded in a stone.
        </description>
        <id_code>PX1-767</id_code>
        <symbols>20-2-35-8-26-15</symbols>
        <locked>false</locked>
    </address>

    <address>
        <name>Earth</name>
        <description>
            Earth, the first world, is referred to as the Tauri by the Goa'uld. It is where the Ancients lived and where
            humans first evolved, the planet from which they were taken and seeded among the stars by the Goa'uld. The
            galaxy is populated by the ancient peoples of Earth.
        </description>
        <id_code></id_code>
        <symbols>28-26-5-36-11-29</symbols>
        <locked>false</locked>
    </address>

    <address>
        <name>Alpha Site</name>
        <description>
            P3X-984 is a world of scattered forests and rocky hills. Because its address was unknown to the Goa'uld, it
            was chosen as the location of the Alpha Site, the off-world base established by the SGC. The secrecy of the
            base was strictly guarded, and it became a sanctuary for refugees among the Rebel Jaffa and the Tok'ra.
        </description>
        <id_code>P3X-984</id_code>
        <symbols>29-5-36-6-23-?</symbols>
        <locked>false</locked>
    </address>

</addresses>